{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992282857","data":{"timestamp":" 947992282857"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992312493","data":{"timestamp":" 947992312493"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992317140","data":{"timestamp":" 947992317140"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 74f2ab9e-516f-4d3a-b9d6-5b1c4034d55e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992326560","data":{"timestamp":" 947992326560"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992326783","data":{"timestamp":" 947992326783"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992327746","data":{"timestamp":" 947992327746"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992329019","data":{"timestamp":" 947992329019"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992331924","data":{"timestamp":" 947992331923"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992332777","data":{"timestamp":" 947992332777"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992333096","data":{"timestamp":" 947992333096"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992334330","data":{"timestamp":" 947992334329"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992337798","data":{"timestamp":" 947992337798"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992338792","data":{"timestamp":" 947992338791"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992339050","data":{"timestamp":" 947992339050"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992340004","data":{"timestamp":" 947992340003"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992342975","data":{"timestamp":" 947992342975"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992344013","data":{"timestamp":" 947992344012"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992344492","data":{"timestamp":" 947992344492"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992349095","data":{"timestamp":" 947992349095"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992349246","data":{"timestamp":" 947992349246"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947992356917","data":{"timestamp":" 947992356917"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995551429","data":{"timestamp":" 947995551429"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995556574","data":{"timestamp":" 947995556574"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" bb901993-0e84-462c-963c-361b4beeb89c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995566565","data":{"timestamp":" 947995566565"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995566793","data":{"timestamp":" 947995566792"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995567771","data":{"timestamp":" 947995567770"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995569051","data":{"timestamp":" 947995569051"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995572068","data":{"timestamp":" 947995572067"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995572926","data":{"timestamp":" 947995572926"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995573247","data":{"timestamp":" 947995573247"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995574490","data":{"timestamp":" 947995574489"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995578152","data":{"timestamp":" 947995578152"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995579146","data":{"timestamp":" 947995579145"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995579411","data":{"timestamp":" 947995579411"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995580363","data":{"timestamp":" 947995580363"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995583272","data":{"timestamp":" 947995583272"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995584326","data":{"timestamp":" 947995584324"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995584812","data":{"timestamp":" 947995584811"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995589435","data":{"timestamp":" 947995589434"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995589588","data":{"timestamp":" 947995589587"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995600734","data":{"timestamp":" 947995600733"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995947158","data":{"timestamp":" 947995947156"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" 5b3ba921-7cd3-42b9-95e5-779a3debebf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995976462","data":{"timestamp":" 947995976462"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995978191","data":{"timestamp":" 947995978191"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995981270","data":{"timestamp":" 947995981270"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995984082","data":{"timestamp":" 947995984082"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995985796","data":{"timestamp":" 947995985796"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995986076","data":{"timestamp":" 947995986076"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947995998214","data":{"timestamp":" 947995998214"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996000596","data":{"timestamp":" 947996000596"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996006207","data":{"timestamp":" 947996006207"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996012172","data":{"timestamp":" 947996012172"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996014307","data":{"timestamp":" 947996014307"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996019477","data":{"timestamp":" 947996019477"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" START_KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996023979","data":{"timestamp":" 947996023979"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996025536","data":{"timestamp":" 947996025536"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996026658","data":{"timestamp":" 947996026658"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996030557","data":{"timestamp":" 947996030556"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" START_KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996042292","data":{"timestamp":" 947996042292"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996047060","data":{"timestamp":" 947996047060"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996048599","data":{"timestamp":" 947996048599"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996050443","data":{"timestamp":" 947996050443"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996059721","data":{"timestamp":" 947996059721"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996067096","data":{"timestamp":" 947996067096"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996069109","data":{"timestamp":" 947996069108"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996071246","data":{"timestamp":" 947996071246"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996073697","data":{"timestamp":" 947996073697"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996076235","data":{"timestamp":" 947996076235"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996077940","data":{"timestamp":" 947996077940"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996093240","data":{"timestamp":" 947996093240"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996095461","data":{"timestamp":" 947996095461"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996097316","data":{"timestamp":" 947996097316"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996098975","data":{"timestamp":" 947996098975"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996102217","data":{"timestamp":" 947996102217"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996104044","data":{"timestamp":" 947996104044"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996104334","data":{"timestamp":" 947996104334"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996105572","data":{"timestamp":" 947996105572"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996107086","data":{"timestamp":" 947996107086"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996109689","data":{"timestamp":" 947996109689"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996110896","data":{"timestamp":" 947996110896"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996113262","data":{"timestamp":" 947996113262"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996113266","data":{"timestamp":" 947996113266"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996113270","data":{"timestamp":" 947996113270"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996116197","data":{"timestamp":" 947996116197"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996116202","data":{"timestamp":" 947996116202"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996116875","data":{"timestamp":" 947996116875"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996117900","data":{"timestamp":" 947996117900"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996118057","data":{"timestamp":" 947996118057"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996132441","data":{"timestamp":" 947996132441"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996133712","data":{"timestamp":" 947996133711"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996135551","data":{"timestamp":" 947996135549"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996135748","data":{"timestamp":" 947996135748"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996139923","data":{"timestamp":" 947996139922"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996141539","data":{"timestamp":" 947996141539"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996145926","data":{"timestamp":" 947996145926"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996149810","data":{"timestamp":" 947996149809"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996154028","data":{"timestamp":" 947996154028"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996156664","data":{"timestamp":" 947996156664"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996160563","data":{"timestamp":" 947996160563"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996162043","data":{"timestamp":" 947996162042"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996162792","data":{"timestamp":" 947996162792"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996162913","data":{"timestamp":" 947996162913"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" ffa09f40-7b71-407a-ac04-3d602e3badc8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996171882","data":{"timestamp":" 947996171882"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996172113","data":{"timestamp":" 947996172113"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996173084","data":{"timestamp":" 947996173083"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996174366","data":{"timestamp":" 947996174366"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996177247","data":{"timestamp":" 947996177247"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996178090","data":{"timestamp":" 947996178090"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996178404","data":{"timestamp":" 947996178404"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996179638","data":{"timestamp":" 947996179638"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996183132","data":{"timestamp":" 947996183132"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996184115","data":{"timestamp":" 947996184115"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996184369","data":{"timestamp":" 947996184369"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996185312","data":{"timestamp":" 947996185312"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996188170","data":{"timestamp":" 947996188170"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996189215","data":{"timestamp":" 947996189214"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996189695","data":{"timestamp":" 947996189695"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996194212","data":{"timestamp":" 947996194210"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996194364","data":{"timestamp":" 947996194364"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947996202430","data":{"timestamp":" 947996202430"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" be0cb5fb-4f8d-4bab-a58c-73d695f90a99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948021475935","data":{"timestamp":" 948021475934"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" b56dfe96-2cff-4d2a-a473-9b7825e6630c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_625_625-379-224"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 625"," userResponse":" 625"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948030796760","data":{"timestamp":" 948030796760"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" d15b5d4a-8839-4910-84f4-07a149da6c2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 259"," userResponse":" 259"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948030811104","data":{"timestamp":" 948030811104"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" d15b5d4a-8839-4910-84f4-07a149da6c2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_625_625-379-224"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 625"," userResponse":" 625"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948030840372","data":{"timestamp":" 948030840372"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000116_061053"," gameId":" d15b5d4a-8839-4910-84f4-07a149da6c2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_625_625-379-224"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}